{
    "subject": "Joanna_of_Castile",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Philip_I_of_Castile",
    "human_readable": "Joanna of Castile is married to Philip I of Castile.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9614759087562561,
            "question": "To whom was Joanna of Castile married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9556295871734619,
            "question": "Who is Joanna of Castile married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9346842765808105,
            "question": "What is the significance of the marriage between Joanna of Castile and Philip I of Castile?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7254482507705688,
            "question": "How did the relationship between Joanna of Castile and Philip I of Castile impact Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.717070996761322,
            "question": "Who were the children of Joanna of Castile and Philip I of Castile?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6518853306770325,
            "question": "What is Philip I of Castile known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6274779438972473,
            "question": "Were there any notable events that occurred during the reign of Joanna of Castile and Philip I of Castile?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5970950722694397,
            "question": "During what period did Joanna of Castile and Philip I of Castile rule?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5126436352729797,
            "question": "Was Joanna of Castile related to the Spanish monarchy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4425688683986664,
            "question": "What is Philip I of Castile's role in history?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joanna of Castile is married to Philip I of Castile.",
            "html": "yago_28447_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Joanna of Castile related to the Spanish monarchy?",
            "html": "yago_28447_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=During what period did Joanna of Castile and Philip I of Castile rule?",
            "html": "yago_28447_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any notable events that occurred during the reign of Joanna of Castile and Philip I of Castile?",
            "html": "yago_28447_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28447_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28447_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28447_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28447_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28447_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28447_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28447_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28447_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28447_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28447_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents indicate that Joanna of Castile was indeed married to Philip the Handsome, who became King of Castile as Philip I after his marriage. Therefore, the statement \"Joanna of Castile is married to Philip I of Castile\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Philip I of Castile is not the correct name for Joanna's husband. He was actually known as Philip the Handsome, Archduke of Austria of the House of Habsburg.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}